<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.example.admin.visitsolapur.McDonalds"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:weightSum="1">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView21"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_weight="0.03"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/mcdonald" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView17"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_weight="0.91"
        android:text="Mcdonalds in Muraraji Peth, Solapur. View Burgers, Happy Meal and Happy Price Menu Of Mcdonalds. Visit Justdial For Mcdonalds Family Restaurants Address, Contact Number, Reviews and  Photos.

Making way for a hearty meal is Mcdonalds Family Restaurant in Solapur. Established in the year 2015, this place is synonymous with delicious food that can satiate all food cravings. It is home to some of the most appreciated cuisines. So as to be able to cater to a large number of diners, it occupies a favourable location at Muraraji Peth. Meena Theatre Near Ajantha Ladge Mechanical Chowk,Shop No 1 Ground Floor Oasis Mall,Muraraji Peth-413002 is where one can visit the venue. Courtesy to this strategic location, foodies in and around the neighborhood can walk in to this eating house conveniently without facing any hassles related to commuting to this part of the city. It is one of the most sought after Restaurants in Muraraji Peth. The www.mcdonaldsindia.com offers complete information of the restaurant. This is a one of the renowned Restaurants in Solapur.

Mcdonalds Family Restaurant at Muraraji Peth makes sure one has a great food experience by offering highly palatable food. The restaurant welcomes guests from 11:00 - 22:00 allowing diners to relish a scrumptious meal between the functional hours.The price range of the food at the restaurant ranges from 1. One can make their payment via Cash, Master Card, Visa Card, Debit Cards, Credit Card. This listing is also listed in Restaurants, Inexpensive Restaurants (Below Rs 500), Fast Food. From a total number of 30+ ratings, the eating house has been rated a 4.1. " />
</LinearLayout>
