<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.example.admin.visitsolapur.UniqueHospital"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:weightSum="1">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView39"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_weight="0.34"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/unihospital1" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView36"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:text="Unique Hospital in Solapur. Hospitals with Address, Contact Number, Photos, Maps. View Unique Hospital, Solapur on Justdial.

In Solapur, Unique Hospital is a recognized name in patient care. It was incepted in the year 1996. They are one of the well-known Hospitals in Solapur City. Backed with a vision to offer the best in patient care and equipped with technologically advanced healthcare facilities, they are one of the upcoming names in the healthcare industry. Located in , this hospital is easily accessible by various means of transport. This hospital is also located at South Kasba Near Old Faujdar Chawadi Near Sonya Maruti - Solapur City. A team of well-trained medical staff, non-medical staff and experienced clinical technicians work round-the-clock to offer various services . Their professional services make them a sought after Hospitals in Solapur. A team of doctors on board, including specialists are equipped with the knowledge and expertise for handling various types of medical cases.

At Unique Hospital in Solapur City, the various modes of payment accepted are Cash, Cheques. You can reach them at ,Near Faujdar Tawdi, South Kasba,Main Road,Solapur City-413007. The contact number of this hospital is +(91)-217-2323211,2723688,2626151. This establishment has been rated a 4.2 from a total of 120+ ratings. This listing is also listed in Hospitals, General Physician Doctors, Gynaecologist and Obstetrician Doctors."
        android:layout_weight="0.62" />

</LinearLayout>
